scranton.edu 2016-10-06

# Scranton.edu Privacy Policy | PIR | The University of Scranton

## Our Commitment to Privacy 

We are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintain the following Privacy Policy to protect the personal information you provide online. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point that personally identifiable information may be requested. Questions regarding this policy should be directed to: [info@scranton.edu](mailto:info@scranton.edu).

## Collection and Use of Information

We will only collect your personal information (such as your name, address, or telephone number) if you provide it voluntarily. If you do not want this information to be collected by us, please do not submit it. We will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purpose for which it is collected. 

In addition, in the course of using our site we automatically track certain information about you. This information includes the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you go to next (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address. Many sites automatically collect this information.

We only use the information that is provided through our site to help us improve our services to you, to provide you with the products you have requested, to inform you about additional products or services that may be of interest to you, for marketing purposes and for other internal purposes. We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending mail and processing event registration. We will only provide these companies with the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. Other than what is described, we do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others outside of our own entity and our advertising and promotional agencies and consultants. If you do not wish to receive this information, please contact us at [info@scranton.edu](mailto:info@scranton.edu).

At any time, while accessing our site, any user, while online, may decline participation in any activity that asks for information (i.e. survey email). Your choice not to participate will in no way affect your ability to use any other feature on our site.

## External Web Sites

To the extent hyperlinks or banner advertisements incorporating hyperlinks are utilized to access third party sites, you should be aware that these third party web sites are not controlled by us and, therefore, are not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should check the privacy policies of these individual sites to see how the operators of those third party web sites will utilize your personal information.

## Google AdWords

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the [CLIENT NAME] website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads), and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.

## Your Consent

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by us. We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept these changes. You may have the right to access the personal information that we have collected about you. You may also have the right to modify any errors contained in that information. Please contact us for more details.

## How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please send us an e-mail at: [info@scranton.edu](mailto:info@scranton.edu).
